dracodirectory.com 2017-12-29

# privacy policy

### Privacy Policy

Dracodirectory.com is the sole owner of the information collected on our directory. We collect information from our users at several different points on our web site. To this end, we have prepared the following privacy policy to ensure all measures are taken to protect the interests of our visitors and provide a more pleasant site experience. ****

**Information Collection**

Submission

During the Dracodirectory.com Submit service, we require information from the user on our submit form. A user must provide contact information (such as name amd email). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest.

Information Use

Profile

We store information that we collect through log files, and via the information provided during the Dracodirectory.com submit service, to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their characteristics. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the user experience. We DO NOT share your profile with other third parties.

Log Files

Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. ****

Communications from the Site

Special Offers and Updates

Established members will occasionally receive information on new services, offers or special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications - these communications are not promotional in nature.

Sharing

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Third Party Intermediaries

We use Paypal to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Dracodirectory.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

Security

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. ****

Notice of Change

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
